Guide to the Federal Theatre Project photograph collection, 1936-1939
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 1: Production Photographs, 1936-1939; (84 boxes)
  - Counselor-at-Law -- Set photographs, March 29, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Counselor-at-Law, March 29, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Counselor-at-Law, March 29, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Coxe, Maria -- Author of "If Ye Break Faith,", 1930s (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Cradle Snatchers (Los Angeles, California), July 13, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cradle Snatchers (San Diego, California), September 29, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cradle Snatchers (San Diego, California), September 29, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Cradle Snatchers (San Diego, California), September 29, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - The Cradle Will Rock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - The Cradle Will Rock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - The Cradle Will Rock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - The Cradle Will Rock (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Cradle Will Rock, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Created Equal (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Created Equal (Newark, New Jersey and Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - The Cricket on the Hearth (San Francisco, California), December 1937 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Cricket on the Hearth (San Francisco, California), December 11, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - The Cricket on the Hearth (San Francisco, California), December 11, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Criminal at Large (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Criminal at Large (Denver, Colorado), August 20, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Criminal at Large (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Criminal at Large (Miami, Florida), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Criminal at Large (Miami, Florida), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Criminal at Large (Hempstead, New York), April 20, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Criminal at Large (Hempstead, New York), April 20, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Criminal at Large (Hempstead, New York), April 20, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Criminal at Large (Hempstead, New York), April 20, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Criminal at Large -- High School (Hempstead, New York), April 30, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Criminal at Large (Syracuse, New York), October 22, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - The Crock of Gold (Los Angeles, California), March 1936 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - The Crock of Gold -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 13, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Crock of Gold -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 13, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Crocodile (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 29, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - The Curtain Goes Up (Seattle, Washington), November 13, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - The Curtain Goes Raises (Salem, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Curtain Goes Raises (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Dailey, Dan -- Sing for Your Supper, 1930s (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Dance (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Dance (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Dance -- Awards (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Dance (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Dance -- Auditions (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Dance -- Dancers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dance -- Rehearsal (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), August 25, 1938 and February 27, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Dance -- Rehearsal (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Dance of Death (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - A Dance Program for Young Folk (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - A Dance Program for Young Folk (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - A Dance Program for Young Folk (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Davy Crockett (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Davy Crockett (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Days Without End (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Days Without End (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Days Without End (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Days Without End (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Death Takes the Wheel -- Marionette (Buffalo, New York), October 14, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Death Takes the Wheel -- Marionette (White Plains, New York), May 25, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Death Takes the Wheel -- Marionette, 1930s (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - The Devil Passes (San Francisco, California), December 22, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - The Devil Passes (San Francisco, California), December 22, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - The Devil Passes (San Francisco, California), December 22, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Devil Passes (San Francisco, California), December 22, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Denver, Colorado), June 20, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Atlanta, Georgia), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Atlanta, Georgia), November 26, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Devil's Disciple (Chicago, Illinois), November 25, 1937 - January 15, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Die Apostel (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Diff'rent (Roslyn, New York), November 24, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Diff'rent (Roslyn, New York), November 24, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Diff'rent (Roslyn, New York), November 24, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Doctor Faustus (Atlanta, Georgia), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Doctor Faustus (Atlanta, Georgia), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Doctor Faustus (Boston, Massachusetts), September 15, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Doctor Faustus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Doctor Faustus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Doctor Faustus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Doctor Faustus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Doctor Faustus (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Doctor Faustus (Roslyn, New York), September 15, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Martin and co. magic and illusion, 1930s (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Doctor Wespie (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Don Quixote -- Marionette (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Don Quixote -- Marionette (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Double Door (San Diego, California), September 15, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Double Door (San Diego, California), September 15, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Double Door (San Diego, California), September 15, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Double Door (San Diego, California), September 15, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Dover Road (San Diego, California), August 17, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The Dover Road (San Diego, California), August 17, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Dover Road (San Diego, California), August 17, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Dover Road (San Diego, California), August 18, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Dover Road (Salem, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dracula (Los Angeles, California), February 15, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Dracula (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - The Dragon Snee Zee -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - The Dragon Snee Zee -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Dragon Snee Zee -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - The Dragon's Tale -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Dragon's Wishbone -- Marionette (Denver, Colorado), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Dragon's Wishbone -- Marionette (Denver, Colorado), October 7, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - The Dragon's Wishbone -- Marionette (Denver, Colorado), October 7, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - The Dragon's Wishbone -- Vaudeville Unit (Tampa, Florida), February 19, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - The Drunkard (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - The Drunkard (New Orleans, Louisiana), February 10, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - The Drunkard (Holyoke, Massachusetts), September 8, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Duley (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Dus Groise Gevins (Boston, Massachusetts), December 6, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Dus Groise Gevins (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - East is West (Los Angeles, California), November 30, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - East is West (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Edson, Eda -- Follow the Parade (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Enimal Mensch (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - El Nino Judio (Tampa, Florida), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 2, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 2, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 2, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (San Francisco, California), April 2, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (San Francisco, California and Boston, Massachussets), 1930s (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette (Boston, Massachusetts), February 10, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Emperor Jones -- Marionette, February 10, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Emperor's New Clothes -- Federal Children's Theatre, 1930s (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (Miami, Florida), December 23, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Emperor's New Clothes (Cleveland, Ohio), June 5, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The End of the Beginning (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Enemy of the People (Los Angeles, California), June 9, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Enemy of the People (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Enemy of the People (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Enemy of the People (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Engaged (Jacksonville, Florida), August 16, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Engaged (Miami, Florida), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Esto no Pasara Aqui (Tampa, Florida), November 1, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Eternal Prodigal (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Eternal Prodigal (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Eternal Prodigal (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Eternal Wanderer (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Ethiopia (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Ethiopia (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - An Evening with Dunbar (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Everyman (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Everyman (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Everyman (Jacksonville, Florida), November 30, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Excursion (Los Angeles, California), May 3, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Excursion (San Francisco, California), July 8, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Excursion (San Francisco, California), July 8, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Excursion (San Francisco, California), July 8, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Excursion (San Francisco, California), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Excursion (Atlanta, Georgia), October 22, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Excursion (Boston and Salem, Massachusetts), November 10, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions -- Madame Sikelianos Exhibit (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions -- Marionettes (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Exhibitions -- Museum of Modern Art (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions -- 71st Armory (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Exhibitions -- Women's Expositions (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Fair and Warmer (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Fair and Warmer (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fair and Warmer (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Family Upstairs (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Fantasy 1939 -- Dance (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Fantasy 1939 -- Dance (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Fantasy 1939 -- Dance (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - The Farmer Takes a Wife (San Francisco, California), July 27, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - The Farmer Takes a Wife (San Francisco, California), July 27, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - The Farmer Takes a Wife (Miami, Florida), May 28, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - The Farmer Takes a Wife (Boston and Salem, Massachusetts), January 6, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - The Farmer Takes a Wife (Boston and Salem, Massachusetts), January 6, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Federal Art Project, 1930s (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Federal Ballet -- Chicago Dance (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Federal Ballet -- Chicago Dance (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Federal Ballet -- Chicago Dance (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Federal Ballet -- Chicago Dance, 1st edition (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Federal Ballet -- Chicago Dance, 2nd edition (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Federal Ballet -- Ruth Page and Bentley Stone, 1930s (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Federal Housing Exposition (White Plains, New York), May 13 - 14, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Federal Music Project -- Madison Square Garden (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Auto registration (New York City, New York), 1938 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Time Sheet (Albany, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Productions Chart (Roslyn, New York), 1939 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Productions Charts (Roslyn, New York), 1939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Research (Roslyn, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Federal Theatre Project -- Workshop (Hempstead, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Federal Varieties (Syracuse, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ferdinand the Bull -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ferdinand the Bull -- Marionette (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ferdinand the Bull, 1930s (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ferdinand the Bull, 1930s (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Festival of American Dance (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Festival of American Dance (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Festival of American Dance (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - The Field God -- Negro (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - The Firebrand (Miami, Florida), January 2, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The Fireman's Flame (Atlanta, Georgia), April 28, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - The First Legion (San Francisco, California), April - July 1936 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - The First Legion (San Francisco, California), April - July 1936 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - The First Legion (San Francisco, California), May 11, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - The First Man (Boston, Massachusetts), October 29, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The First Mrs. Fraser (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - The First Mrs. Fraser (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Flanagan, Hallie, 1930s (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Hallie Flanagan with radio microphone, 1936
  - Flanagan, Hallie, 1930s (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Flanagan, Hallie, 1930s (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Flight (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Flight (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Flight (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Flight (Seattle, Washington), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - The Florist Shop (Muskogee, Oklahoma), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fly Away Home (Salem, Massachusetts), February 2, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fly Away Home (Salem, Massachusetts), February 2, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Follow the Parade (Los Angeles, California), April 1, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Follow the Parade, April 1, 1936
    - Follow the Parade, April 1, 1936
  - Follow the Parade (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Follow the Parade (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Follow the Parade (Tampa, Florida), May 25, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Follow the Parade -- On tour (Dallas, Texas), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Texas Bowl, 1936
    - Stage at the Texas Centennial Exposition, 1936
  - Folson, Robert, 1930s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - The Fool (Oakland, California), September 8, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Fool (San Diego, California), December 26, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - The Fool (San Diego, California), December 26, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Frankie and Johnny -- Federal Ballet (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Frankie and Johnny -- Federal Ballet (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Frankie and Johnny -- Federal Ballet (Chicago, Illinois), 1937 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Free, Adult, Uncensored, 1930s (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Freeport Relief Committee (Freeport, New York), September 17, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Fresh Fields (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Fresh Fields (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Fresh Fields (Cedarhurst, New York), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Genesis (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Genesis (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Genesis (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Genesis (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (San Diego, California), May 11, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (San Diego, California), May 11, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (San Diego, California), May 11, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (Roslyn, New York), November 14, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (Roslyn, New York), November 14, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes (Roslyn, New York), 1938 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Gerwing, George -- Western Division, 1930s (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The Ghost Train (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The Ghost Train (San Diego, California), August 18, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The Ghost Train (San Diego, California), August 18, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Ghost Train (Peoria, Illinois), August-September 1937 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Gilbert and Sullivan (Brooklyn, New York), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Gilbert and Sullivan -- Traveling (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (San Diego, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (San Diego, California), October 20, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (San Diego, California), October 20, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (Jacksonville, Florida), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - The Girl of the Golden West (Jacksonville, Florida), April 4, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Girl Wants Glamour (Tacoma, Washington), September 19, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Girl Wants Glamour (Tacoma, Washington), September 19, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Gleason, Adda (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - God of Vengeance -- Yiddish (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - God of Vengeance -- Yiddish (Los Angeles, California), January 6, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - God of Vengeance -- Yiddish (Los Angeles, California), January 6, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Gods of the Lightning (Los Angeles, California), September 1, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Gods of the Lightning (Los Angeles, California), September 1, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Gods of the Lightning (Los Angeles, California), September 1, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Gods of the Lightning (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - The Gondoliers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - The Gondoliers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - The Gondoliers (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - The Good Fairy (Freeport, New York), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - The Good Old Summertime (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - The Good Old Summertime, 1930s (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - The Goose Hangs High (Los Angeles, California), December 14, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - The Goose Hangs High (Los Angeles, California), December 14, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Government Projects -- C.C.C. (Maine), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Government Projects -- C.C.C. (Oklahoma), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - The Great Barrington (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - The Great Barrington (Los Angeles, California), February 16 - 17, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - The Great Barrington (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - The Great Barrington (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - The Great Barrington (Boston, Massachusetts), April 14, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - The Great Catherine (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Great Catherine (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs (Los Angeles, California), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs (Los Angeles, California), January 6, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs (Miami, Florida), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs (Salem, Massachusetts), April 6, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Green Grow the Lilacs (Cincinnati, Ohio), October 7, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Guns and Castanets -- Federal Ballet (Chicago, Illinois), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Gypsy Lullaby -- Children (Gary, Indiana), April 10, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Habit (Los Angeles, California), February 10, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Habit (Los Angeles, California), February 10, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Haiti -- Alvin Childress (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Haiti (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Haiti (Hartford, Connecticut), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Haiti (Boston, Massachusetts), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Haiti (Boston, Massachusetts), October 29 - November 6, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Haiti (Boston, Massachusetts), October 29 - November 6, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Haiti -- Negro (New York City, New York), 1930s (Box 29, Folder 18)